That a very big life insurance
company of India whose name is Aditya Birla Sun Life
Insurance has such a policy
in which you can subscribe for only one lakh rupees, I am going to
tell you about this in detail about subscription,
so please try to understand the video and
we can
get a lot of money here and I will show you with examples,
I Yogendra Yogi
welcome you very much to my YouTube channel
and through this video I will make it
clear that after taking this policy
we will get more, we will roll this roti,
you should I think you will
definitely get subscribers for this, for this
you will have to take a plan
through Finance and Sandeep Singh and Midfielder or write online policy
through His Mother & Son Secure, the
minimum premium of this plan is 50 but if you take ₹1 then
whatever details are shown here, we are
showing on premium of ₹1 only, what
benefit you get, take a premium of ₹1000,
its entry fee is 250 for five years
Any person can be killed if he publishes articles.
I would like to inform you that this policy is a Yukta
and people in this group take pornographic material. There are
two options available in this policy, one
option is to subscribe and you will get total income
every year by
subscribing and the other option is to
update it and the next option is that you will keep getting
regular income, you will get
₹2 subscription for every album you play.
Please subscribe to this channel,
definitely subscribe, but the
subscribe and
quiz inside you and the 13 year old at home says the day after tomorrow it
seems the torn near talk will be returned, the number of
people who were subscribed did
not subscribe, they did subscribe
and the appointments happen
after the world, there is a gap in this, if
we do not make a gap then what will happen if
you subscribe but you were subscribed,
which you might be thinking and
subscribe, I am not doing anything wrong in this,
you use it in your account,
you subscribe and in your subscription, you
easily get a return of up to 20 percent from this question, those who now
take the torn appointment policy, Rabbit
Meghnad Subscribe  So you can convert it into which I am
subscribing,
so subscribe, subscribe and if you
subscribe to this, then cover it from here, if you
enter the monthly amount of rupees, then it becomes sixteen something,
about 16500, if you
subscribe, then 6, so if you
subscribe and this is not a subscription
from the company, from here you will get two
quick calculations, I have calculated it and
I will show it to you by clicking on the skin, if you
see it, as soon as we enter its
investment details, I calculated it
like this, but you are seeing that
in our actual 639006, if you subscribe to it, then it is a
very big thing, and if you see
subscription, then subscribe to this channel, then
subscribe to it, so please
watch it, if you liked the video, if you
felt that I got some knowledge from it, by
changing some investment path and combing, we do
not get subscription, insurance
subscription and you get collection of money, that is why
I would say to you, if you liked it, then
definitely subscribe to this video and
please definitely subscribe in the comment box,
hello friends, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat